Guide to The Nation Records TAM.682
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Center for Democracy; KH, 1984-1988 (Box 323)
- Typescript and Manced Galleys (Incomplete); Naming Names (1/2), Undated (Box 324)
- SCW Nominees: Renquist, Scalia, Kennedy (2/2), 1971-1986 (Box 325)
- SCW Boris (1/2), 1982-1987 (Box 326)
- Katrina Vanden Heuevel Correspondence M-Z (1/2), 1994 (Box 327)
- Dialogo, Undated (Box 328)
- Carey McWilliams Correspondence File (3/3_, 1960-1975 (Box 329)
- Typescript and Manced Galleys (Incomplete); Naming Names (2/2), Undated (Box 330)
- SCW Potential Nominees Pre-1990 A-N (2/2), 1984-1990 (Box 331)
- Press Releases/Publicity (2/2), 1984-1986 (Box 332)
- SCW Potential Nominees Pre-1990 A-N (1/2), 1984-1990 (Box 333)
- Carey McWilliams Correspondence File (2/3), 1960-1975 (Box 334)
- Carey McWilliams Correspondence File (1/3), 1960-1975 (Box 335)
- Fact Finding Trips/Tours (1/2), 1984-1986 (Box 336)
- Press Releases/Publicity (1/2), 1984-1986 (Box 337)
- Alger Hiss; Videos 21; Footnotes; Nation Institute (1/2), Undated (Box 338)
- SCW Nominees: Renquist, Scalia, Kennedy (1/2), 1971-1986 (Box 339)
- CDST Deposit Reports (2/2), 1990-1993 (Box 340)
- Victor Navasky General and Specific Files #11 (2/2), 1980-1981 (Box 341)
- Nation Institute Conferences as Far Back as 1979 (2/2), Undated (Box 342)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence File #14 (1/2), 1984 (Box 343)
- Nation Ford Memoirs #2 (1/2), 1984 (Box 344)
- A. Cockburn Papers; Miscellaneous Criminal Law Monthly (1/2), Undated (Box 345)
- Joan Wypijewski: Art Poll (1/2), Undated (Box 346)
- Joan Wypijewski: Art Poll (2/2), Undated (Box 347)
- Joan Wypijewski: Kopkind Book (1/2), Undated (Box 348)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence File #14 (2/2), 1984 (Box 349)
- Navasky Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 350)
- Circulation ledgers, 1989-1990 (Box 351)
- Student Nation, Undated (Box 352)
- Article Submissions, 1984-1985 (Box 353)
- FOIA Day Event Planning/ Great Debates- PBS, Undated (Box 354)
- IN N/P (2/2), Undated (Box 355)
- Joan Wypijewski: Kopkind Book (2/2), Undated (Box 356)
- Conference on the Journal of Critical Opinion, Undated (Box 357)
- Circulation Ledgers (1/2), 1991 (Box 358)
- Victor Navasky Day Planners and Appointment Books, 1979-1993 (Box 359)
- Katrina Vanden Heuevel Files (1/2), 1997-2008 (Box 360)
- Victor Navasky N-P (1/2), Undated (Box 362)
- McWilliams #19 (2/2), Undated (Box 364)
- Assorted Letters to the Editor (2/2), 1990-1994 (Box 365)
- Assorted Letters to the Editor (1/2), 1990-1994 (Box 366)
- Peggy; List Sales; Name in the News (1/2), 1987 (Box 367)
- McWilliams #19 (1/2), Undated (Box 368)
- SCW Fundraising and Administrative, 1985-1990 (Box 369)
- Hamilton Fish Files (2/2), 1980-1983 (Box 370)
- SCW Potential Nominees N-Z, 1984-1990 (Box 371)
- Hamilton Fish Files (1/2), 1980-1983 (Box 372)
- Potential SCW Nominees: D. Ginsburg, E. Meese (1/2), 1985-1987 (Box 373)
- Press Releases (2/2), 1985-1989 (Box 374)
- SCW Bork/Kennedy (2/2), 1987-1988 (Box 375)
- SCW Bork/Kennedy (1/2), 1987-1988 (Box 376)
- Nation Anthology KVH (2/2), 1987-1988 (Box 377)
- Nation Anthology KVH (1/2), 1987-1988 (Box 378)
- Press Releases (1/2), 1985-1989 (Box 379)
- Journalism Prizes and Awards; Tables of Contents; Magazine; Nation Institute (1/2), 1980-1986 (Box 380)
- Letters Unpublished (2/2), 2004 (Box 381)
- A. Cockburn Papers (2/2), Undated (Box 382)
- Letters to the Editor: Unpublished (2/3, 1993-1995 (Box 383)
- Letters to the Editor: Unpublished (3/3), 1993-1995 (Box 384)
- Stephen Soule Files, 1983 (Box 385)
- Letters to the Editor, 1998 (Box 386)
- VN Drafts of A Matter of an Opinion 1/5, 2001-2005 (Box 387)
- Letters to the Editor Unpublished (1/3), 1993-1995 (Box 388)
- VN Drafts of A Matter of an Opinion 2/5, Undated (Box 389)
- Pre 1990 (The Micah Years); Random Letters to the Editor, before 1990 (Box 390)
- Letters to the Editor, 2003 (Box 391)
- VN Drafts of A Matter of an Opinion 3/5, Undated (Box 392)
- VN Drafts of A Matter of an Opinion 4/5, Undated (Box 393)
- Victor Navasky Letters to the Editor (2/2), 1997 (Box 394)
- Allan Nairn (1/2), Undated (Box 395)
- VN Drafts of A Matter of an Opinion 5/5, Undated (Box 396)
- Victor Navasky Letters to the Editor (1/2), 1997 (Box 397)
- Letters Unpublished (1/2), 2004 (Box 398)
- Nation Institute: Boston Roundtable Tour to Israel; Reader and Tapes (1/2), 1984-1985 (Box 399)
- Nation Institute Conferences as Far Back as 1979; Rosenburg Great Debate; Investigative Fund (South Africa); Tax Papers from the 1970s-1990s; IF Stone (FOIA); Nicagaruan Papers; Potential Investors; Stock Information (1/2) (Box 400)
- J. Wypijewski: Story Files, Correspondence; Wash BAB; Art Poll (1/2), 1990s, undated (Box 401)
- J. Wypijewski: Story Files, Correspondence; Wash BAB; Art Poll (2/2), 1990s, undated (Box 402)
- Allan Nairn (2/2), Undated (Box 403)
- Letters to the Editor (2/2), 1987-1992 (Box 407)
- Letters to the Editor (1/2), 1987-1992 (Box 409)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence File #1, 1978-1979 (Box 138)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence (1/2), 1983 (Box 405)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence (2/2), 1983 (Box 408)
- Editorial Correspondence (1/2), 1982 (Box 404)
- Office Files, undated (Box 415)
- Office Files, 1956-2005 (Box 361, Box 363)
- Office Files, 1956-2005 (Box 416, Box 417, Box 418, Box 419, Box 420, Box 421, Box 422)
- Victor Navasky Correspondence, 1993 (Box 423)
- Office Files, 1956-2005 (Box 412, Box 413, Box 414)
- Allain Nairn #2/IND/GNAT/ES, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 424)